Little bunny, stop hiding.
It's you again, as expected.
I've loved listening to your piano playing since I was little.
So many years have passed.
You humans
age so quickly, don't you?
Even if another ten thousand years pass, I will still look the same.
I've loved listening to you play the piano since I was a child.
Even if ten thousand years pass, I will still feel the same.
But you, why do you come here every day?
What, are you trying to mess with my mind?
Annoying.
I've already told you, I like you.
I've been practicing for many years, and I've sealed off my emotions long ago.
So, you better not waste your time.
I don't care, I want to be with you.
Just because you say so?
What benefits can you bring me?
I... I...
I can protect you.
An unexpected guest has arrived.
Little rabbit, you better protect yourself first.
Thanks, Dad.
Lin Zhan, I've finally found you.
As long as I drink your blood,
I will soon greatly increase my power and achieve immortality!